Huh?
啊？
Get away from me money!
钱离我远点！
Daddy! Daddy!
爸爸！爸爸！
I finally figured out
what you can get me
我终于想通了
你能给我什么
for my birthday next week!
下周是我的生日！
I found the perfect boat
for you to buy me!
我找到了完美的船
为了你买我！
Boat?
船？
I never said I'd buy you
a birthday boat!
我从来没有说过要买你
生日船！
Pearl!
珍珠！
If you stop playing that
earsplitting music,
如果你停止玩这个游戏
震耳欲聋的音乐，
I'll buy you a new boat
for your birthday!
我会给你买一艘新船
为了你的生日！
You're not recording me,
are ya?
你没有给我录音，
你是吗？
It's the only boat for me
and it's only 10,000 clams!
这是我唯一的船
而且只有一万只蛤蜊！
T-t-t-t-ten!
十、十！
Th-th-th-thousand?
第、第、千？
Gonna get a new boat!
I'm not bratty!
要去买一艘新船了！
我不淘气！
A birthday boat!
From my daddy!
生日船！
来自我爸爸！
Me and my big mouth!
我和我的大嘴！
There it is, SpongeBob,
me daughter's birthday boat!
就在那里，海绵宝宝，
我女儿的生日船！
I love it!
我喜欢它！
Not the brochure!
不是宣传册！
Oooh!
噢！
Nice fixer-upper,
漂亮的固定器上部，
but why didn't you just buy
a new boat?
但你为什么不直接买
一艘新船？
Because I'm not paying
10,000 clams for a new boat.
因为我不付钱
一艘新船需要 10,000 只蛤蜊。
You're gonna help me
fix up this boat
你会帮助我的
修好这艘船
so it's as good
as the brochure boat!
所以也一样好
作为宣传册船！
Me Pearl will never know
the difference.
我珍珠永远不会知道
差异。
This may take a while.
这可能需要一段时间。
One "a while" later...
“一会儿”之后...
Zow-ie!
Zow-ie！
This boat looks like it costs
a million clams!
这艘船看起来很贵
一百万只蛤蜊！
Well, at least on the outside.
嗯，至少在外面是这样。
Now we just gotta find an engine
before Pearl wakes up.
现在我们只需要找到一个引擎
在珍珠醒来之前。
My birthday!
我的生日！
We gotta hide!
我们得躲起来！
Pearl's a-coming, boy-o!
珍珠来了，小伙子！
Yow!
哟！
Gonna get a new boat!
I'm not bratty!
要去买一艘新船了！
我不淘气！
A birthday boat!
From my daddy!
生日船！
来自我爸爸！
B-O-A-T!
船！
Boat?
船？
It's the boat that I wanted!
这就是我想要的船！
I love my daddy!
我爱我的爸爸！
I'll take a test drive!
That's the stuff!
我去试驾一下！
就是这样的东西！
I'll be back
before Daddy wakes up!
我会回来的
在爸爸醒来之前！
She can't drive a boat
with no engine.
她不会驾驶船
没有引擎。
- Hey, Pearl!
- Quiet!
- 嘿，珍珠！
- 安静的！
She can't find out
this is a piece of junk!
她查不出来
这是一块垃圾！
Well, how will we do that?
那么，我们该怎么做呢？
Fake it!
We'll be the engine!
假装吧！
我们将成为引擎！
Uh...
呃...
Vroom, vroom!
呜呜呜！
Let's open her up
and see what this baby can do!
让我们打开她的心扉
看看这个宝宝能做什么！
Boy-Bob, me sponge...
男孩鲍勃，我海绵......
You're on axle duty!
你正在轮轴值班！
Aye-Aye, Cap'n!
是啊，船长！
- Ooh! A navigation system!
- Ow!
- 哦！导航系统！
- 噢！
What's the quickest route
to Bikini Bottom High School?
最快的路线是什么
去比基尼高中？
I want to pick up my friends!
我要接我的朋友们！
Friends?
朋友们？
I don't want any greasy
teenagers in this boat!
我不想要任何油腻的东西
这艘船上的青少年！
- What?
- Uh, I mean...
- 什么？
- 呃，我的意思是...
Turn left at the intersection.
Bing!
在路口左转。
宾！
Honk-honk!
喇叭喇叭！
Cool boat, Pearl!
酷船，珍珠！
Quit gawking, girls,
and hop in!
别再傻眼了，姑娘们，
跳进去！
Pearl! Pearl! Pearl!
珍珠！珍珠！珍珠！
Pearl! Let's have some music!
珍珠！让我们来点音乐吧！
What? SpongeBob!
什么？海绵宝宝！
Start singing!
开始唱歌吧！
My ears!
Ugh! Shut it off!
我的耳朵！
啊!关掉它！
Whoa!
哇！
I hope they didn't crack
my shell open!
我希望它们没有破裂
我的壳打开了！
Oof! Hit the brakes, boy-o!
钱币！踩刹车，孩子！
Hey, nice wheels, Pearl.
嘿，漂亮的轮子，珍珠。
I never thought an old skinflint
like your dad
我从没想过一个老顽皮的人
像你爸爸一样
would buy you a boat!
会给你买条船！
Who's this hoodlum calling old?
这个流氓叫谁老？
Take a hike, Sharkface!
去远足吧，鲨鱼脸！
Unless you want a shark race?
除非你想要一场鲨鱼竞赛？
Ooh!
哦！
A cheerleader race, huh?
啦啦队比赛，是吧？
Hold on to your pom-poms!
抓紧你的绒球！
Ra-ra-ra!
啦啦啦！
R-r-r-race?
R-R-R-竞赛？
Oh no!
哦不！
A race?
一场比赛？
Oh yes!
哦是的！
Take a break, SpongeBob.
休息一下吧，海绵宝宝。
This pompadoured punk is mine!
这个留着浓密头发的小混混是我的！
Mr. Krabs, don't you think
we should slow down a little?
蟹老板，你不觉得吗
我们应该放慢一点吗？
We can't slow down now!
我们现在不能放慢脚步！
I got this snot-nose
right where I want him!
我有这个鼻涕
就在我想要他的地方！
Pearl! Pearl! Pearl! Pearl!
珍珠！珍珠！珍珠！珍珠！
Sink your teeth into those!
把你的牙齿埋进去吧！
Oh, the agony of defeat!
哦，失败的痛苦！
That's it, boy-o!
I need all your legs!
就是这样，男孩！
我需要你所有的腿！
As fast as you can grow 'em!
尽可能快地种植它们！
Ooh! I smell a plan!
哦！我闻到了计划的味道！
Go get 'em, boat!
Sic 'em!
快去抓住他们吧，船！
死吧！
Cheerleaders should stay
on their astro-turf
啦啦队应该留下来
在他们的太空草皮上
and off the road!
并离开道路！
You seem to have dropped these.
你好像把这些都丢掉了。
Mommy!
妈妈！
My heart is racing faster
than those sharks!
我的心跳得更快
比那些鲨鱼！
I want more excitement!
我想要更多的刺激！
More thrills!
更多惊险刺激！
More vehicular mayhem!
更多车辆混乱！
Yeah, like a demolition derby!
是的，就像一场拆除德比！
What?
什么？
Yeah, like a demolition derby!
是的，就像一场拆除德比！
Who said that?
That's a great idea!
谁说的？
这是个好主意！
My boat is invincible!
我的船是无敌的！
Hello, boys!
哈喽，孩子们！
Pearl, Pearl!
She's our whale!
珍珠，珍珠！
她是我们的鲸鱼！
She is much too big to fail!
她太大了，不能失败！
Go, Pearl!
走吧，珍珠！
Here's my Pearl Girl Twirl Hurl!
这是我的珍珠女孩旋转投掷！
If we don't get out of here,
Pearl's gonna get us killed!
如果我们不离开这里
珀尔会害死我们的！
How about a Blowhole Blast!
气孔爆炸怎么样！
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
哇哇哇！
Pearl! Pearl! Pearl!
珍珠！珍珠！珍珠！
Whoo-hoo!
呼呼！
What a rush!
多么匆忙啊！
I'm a demolition whale, baby!
我是一头破坏鲸，宝贝！
Oh, no!
哦，不！
What did I do to my new boat?
我对我的新船做了什么？
Daddy's gonna kill me!
爸爸要杀了我！
Uh-oh, that doesn't sound good.
呃哦，这听起来不太好。
Sounds like my dad
in the bathroom.
听起来像我爸爸
在浴室里。
Yeah, sounds to me like
是的，对我来说听起来像
your engine is dying
a slow, agonizing death.
你的引擎快要死了
缓慢而痛苦的死亡。
Let's get it on the lift
and fix 'er up.
让我们把它拿到电梯上
并修复它。
Oh, thank you!
哦，谢谢你！
Ah-ha!
啊哈！
Well, young lady,
I found the trouble...
嗯，年轻的女士，
我发现了麻烦...
You got two knuckleheads
你有两个傻瓜
instead of an engine!
而不是发动机！
Daddy?
爸爸？
What are you doing hiding
inside of my boat?
你躲起来做什么
在我的船里面？
I just wanted to build you
我只是想塑造你
a special boat
for your birthday!
一艘特殊的船
为了你的生日！
Tell her, SpongeBob!
告诉她，海绵宝宝！
Ooh, yeah! I remember!
哦，是啊！我记得！
Mr. Krabs said...
蟹老板说……
I'm not payin'
10,000 clams for a new boat!
我不付钱
一艘新船需要一万只蛤蜊！
Pearl will never know
the difference!
珍珠永远不会知道
区别！
Never mind!
没关系！
Listen to me, Pearl,
I think what we have here
听我说，珍珠，
我想我们这里有什么
is simply a failure
to commiserate!
简直就是失败
表示同情！
I've heard enough
from you, Daddy!
我已经听够了
来自你，爸爸！
You tried to cheap out
like always,
你试图便宜
像往常一样，
and gift me a piece of junk
for my birthday!
并送我一件垃圾
为了我的生日！
Well, when you say it like that
it sounds bad, yeah...
好吧，当你这样说的时候
听起来很糟糕，是的...
Ooh!
哦！
I see the real trouble now.
我现在看到了真正的麻烦。
You got a credit card in
your pocket that needs charging!
您有一张信用卡
你的口袋需要充电！
And I'm gonna charge
a new boat on it!
我要收费
上面有一艘新船！
Ha! Maybe two!
哈!也许两个！
I just happen to have two
new boats for sale right here!
我只是碰巧有两个
新船就在这里出售！
But they're very expensive.
但它们非常昂贵。
Wait, wait, wait, no! Wait!
等等，等等，等等，不！等待！
I got two boats!
I'm not bratty!
我有两艘船！
我不淘气！
I got two boats
to spite my daddy!
我有两艘船
来侮辱我的爸爸！